Warren S. McCulloch Papers 1860s-1987 Mss.B.M139
American Philosophical Society
- Series VIII. Photographs, 1860's-1960's; 9.5 lin. feet
  - Professional
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-427, 1967; 1 item
      G. E. Lowitz
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-428, 1967; 1 item
      R. E. Beckett
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-431, 1967; 1 item
      E. L. Dubrul
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-432, 1967; 1 item
      Colonel H. E. Sheppard
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-433, 1967; 1 item
      Colonel H. A. Snyder
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-434, 1967; 1 item
      Reverend J. Kindschuh
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-435, 1967; 1 item
      Kindschuh, Snyder, Sheppard, Durrenburger, Hudson
    - Von Foerster, Heinz, n.d.; 1 item
    - Winter Haven Lions Research Foundation. Scientific Advisory Board, 1961 May; 2 items
    - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1921; 1 item
  - Personal
    - Aileon, Will, and Taffy Harrowes, 1952 Sept.; 1 vol.
      Visiting MBM in New York City
    - Baboon, n.d.; 1 print
    - Baby photo album, n.d.; 1 small blue
    - Bailey, Percival, n.d.; 1 print
    - Berendsen, Herman, ca. 1960; 4 items
      PhD party
    - Boelive, Mina and David Metzger, 1898; 2 items in leather case
    - Bradley, family photos, ca. 1910; 8 prints
    - Bradley, Lucy, n.d.; 3 prints
    - Bradley, Nina Duncan, n.d.; 1 print
    - Brats Jinx. cat. 1958, 1 item
    - Coquin (Coke). Poodle, 1958-1964; 12 items
    - Davidson family, 1951 Mar. 4; 4 items
      Orphan Homes of Scotland
    - Devil's Hop Yard, Lyme, Connecticut, ca. 1950?; 37 items
      Family outing
    - Du Brul, Lloyd, 1967; 1 item
      In wine cellar with skull. OVERSIZE
    - Duncan, children, 1860-1890; 4 prints
    - Duncan, children in costumes, ca. 1900; 2 photos
    - Duncan, Eliza Lawrence, ca. 1890-1900; 2 prints
    - Duncan, Eliza Lawrence, baptismal record, 1843; 1 item
    - Duncan, Luisa Pollard, ca. 1840; 2 photos
    - Duncan, Martha Callender, 1 glass plate negative
    - Duncan, Martha Callender, 1 glass plate negative
    - Duncan, Mary Pollard, ca. 1860-1890; 4 prints
    - Duncan, Stephen, n.d.; 1 glass plate negative
    - Dusser de Barenne, J. G., 1950s?; 3 items
    - Eastern States Horse Show, 1960; 1 print
    - Enlisted basic submarine course, SS-475 Argonaut, 1953; 2 prints
    - Farm. Animals and landscape, 7 items
    - Farm. Building the "Garage", 1950's; 31 items
    - Farm. Building under construction, 10 items
    - Farm. Constructing "The Barn", 1950's; 10 items
      10 strips of contact sheets
    - Farm. Girls and horse, undated; 4 items
    - Farm. Man and horse, couple, girls, wagon, 1941; 3 items
    - Farm. People in the pictures, n.d.; 7 items
    - Figures for articles, n.d.; 10 items
    - Friends of Warren McCulloch, 5 prints
    - Irving, Capt. John Duer, 1918; 1 item
    - McCulloch, Abigail, n.d.; 2 prints
    - McCulloch, Abigail Sears, n.d.; 1 print
    - McCulloch, David, ca. 1930; 1 print
    - McCulloch, Elizabeth, ca. 1895; 2 prints
    - McCulloch Family, 1902-1903; 12 items
      WSM with sisters, mother, father
    - McCulloch Family, 1950's-1960's; Folder 2, 13 items
    - McCulloch Family, 1950's-1960's; Folder 1, 15 items
      Color prints
    - McCulloch Family, 1950's-1960's; Folder 3, 7 items
    - McCulloch Family, 1950's-1960's; Folder 4, 7 items
      8" x 10"
    - McCulloch Family, 1952-1964; Folder 5, 50 items
      Mostly taken in Old Lyme, Connecticut. Color slides
    - McCulloch Family, 1957; 11 prints
    - McCulloch Family Album, September 1952; 1 small red
    - McCulloch Family Album at the Orange House, ca. 1910-1926
    - McCulloch, James W., ca. 1882-1910; 15 prints
    - McCulloch, Jean School Album, 1938; 1
    - McCulloch, Jean as a child, 1930-1960; 9 items
    - McCulloch, Jean wedding photos, n.d.; 30 prints
    - McCulloch, Jean, Taffy, Rook and David, ca. 1940; 1 print
    - McCullogh, John, Anna and Warren, ca. 1880; 2 prints
    - McCulloch, Margaret, 1900-1940; 8 prints
    - McCulloch, Mrs. James Wilson, n.d.; 2 items
    - McCulloch, Paul L., 1893 May 6; 1 item
    - McCulloch, Paul L. family, ca.1955; 10 prints
    - McCulloch, Rook, 1968; 8 items
      Negatives
    - McCulloch, Rook, camp legal papers, August 23, 1930; 2 items
    - McCulloch, Rook, miscellaneous photos, 1920-1975; 34 prints
    - McCulloch, Taffy 1, n.d.; 2 prints
    - McCulloch, Taffy 2, n.d.; 11 prints
    - McCulloch, Taffy as a child and with her children, 1930-1960; 14 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S., ca. 1920; 1 item
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1950s?; 1 item
      WSM with Edgar Douglas Adrian, first Baron Adrian, Nobel laureate in Medicine (1932), in front of an exhibit (in Cambridge?)
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1950's'-1960's; Folder 1, 32 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1950's'-1960's; Folder 3, 3 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1960's; 3 items
      Prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1960's; 1 item
      WSM in an academic office. Color print
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1950's'-1960's; Folder 2, 22 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1966; 1 item
      WSM with MIT staff
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1960's; 3 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1966; 1 item
      WSM reading and holding a cigar
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1966; 1 item
      WSM at a blackboard with staff
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1967-1969; 8 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1930's; 1 item
      Portrait
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1969; 1 item
      Photograph inscribed to Heinz Von Foerster
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1940's; 2 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S., ca. 1940-1967; 8 prints, 1 clipping
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1954; 1 item
      8" x 10" color print
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1860's-1960's; Box 2
      Family photographs
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1860's-1960's; Box 3
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1860's-1960's; Box 4
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1860's-1960's; Box 5
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1860's-1960's; Box 6
    - McCulloch, Warren S., 1860's-1960's; 18 boxed volumes
    - McCulloch, Warren S. and family, 4 rolls
    - McCulloch, Warren S. and Florence Kirsh du Brul, ca. 1950; 3 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S. and Margaret, 1908; 1 print
    - McCulloch, Warren S. and Rook, ca. 1960; 3 prints, 14 negatives
    - McCulloch, Warren S. and Rook, Gammie, and Coquin, 1961 May; 4 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S. as a baby, ca. 1900; 3 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S. as a child, ca. 1900-1905; 26 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S. at the farm and in Spain, 1968-1969; 15 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S. early years, ca. 1899-1918; 23 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S. in Greece and Italy, ca. 1963-1969; 5 prints, 3 negatives
    - McCulloch, Warren S. in Memphis, 1956; 3 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S., early years, ca. 1899-1918; 23 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S., Elizabeth and Margaret, ca. 1898-1909; 4 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S., family, and colleagues, 1950's-1960's; 37 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S.,family photos, ca. 1870-1931; 3 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S. with friends and family, ca. 1974; 4 prints, 5 negatives
    - Metzger, David and Mina, ca. 1910-1950; 2 prints
    - Metzger, Margaret, ca. 1920
    - Metzger, Mina, photo of her great grandmother, ca. 1865; 1 print
    - Metzger, Ruth and Margaret, 1905; 3 items
      Playing dress up
    - Miscellaneous family photos, ca. 1900; 20 prints
    - Miscellaneous McCulloch family photos and cards, ca. 1885-1945; 6 items
    - Miscellaneous photos, ca. 1900-1930; 12 prints
    - Miscellaneous photos of Warren with family, n.d.; 6 prints
    - Miscellaneous photos of Warren with family and friends, ca. 1940-1970; 164 prints
    - Miscellaneous prints 1, ca. 1940-1960; 60 prints
    - Miscellaneous prints 2, ca. 1940; 20 prints
    - Miscellaneous wedding photos, n.d.; 2 prints
    - Negatives from Old Lyme 1, n.d.; 21 negatives
    - Negatives from Old Lyme 2, March 19, 1948; 120 negatives
    - Negatives from Old Lyme 3, n.d.; 75 negatives
    - Old Farm House at Chevy Chase, n.d.; 1 print
    - Oldfield, The Calendar of, 1917; 1 item
    - Oldfield, The Catalogue, ca. 1900; 1 item
    - Oldfields and McCulloch family album, 1924; 6 items
    - Owl. Steve Sherwood's, 1967 Dec.; 1 item
      Color print
    - Paintings of flowers, ca. 1866; 24 items
    - Party, Cambridge, Mass., 1964 Oct. 21; 4 items
    - Party, Cambridge, Mass., 1964 Nov. 12; 4 items
    - Pike, Frank, n.d.; 1 print
    - Pitts, Walter, n.d.; 1 print
    - Prescott, Charles Holden, n.d.; 1 print, 1 clipping
    - Scotland 1, 1953 July7; 35 items
      WSM's trip
    - Scotland 2, 3 prints
    - Seitz, Russell, 1969; 4 items
    - Shady Hill Square House, 1964 April; 6 items
    - Souvenir, The Langham, n.d.
    - Surprise party for Rook McCulloch, 1969; 6 items
    - Sy, 1963; 1 print
    - Taffy and Jean at Lyme, ca. 1940; 11 prints
    - Taffy and Steve, ca. 1950; 2 prints
    - Toga Party, n.d.; 1 print
    - Unicorns in Parliament Square, n.d.; 4 items
    - Unidentified, 1966; 1 item
      MIT staff
    - Unidentified baby, n.d.; 6 prints
    - Unidentified boy, 1960; 7 items
      Academic setting, one photo of street scene. From Carter Zeleznik, psychiatry, Jefferson Medical College. Color prints
    - Unidentified boy, n.d.; 1 item
      19th century, studio portrait of boy in 18th century clothes
    - Unidentified man, n.d.; 2 items
      1 negative